<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="about_me">About Me</string>
    <string name="experience">Experience</string>
    <string name="education">Education</string>
    <string name="languages">Languages</string>
    <string name="skills">Skills</string>
    <string name="projects">Projects</string>

    <string name="website">Website</string>
    <string name="present">Present</string>
    <string name="white_label_tip">An app that can be customized with your logo, name, and design</string>
    <string name="copy_message">Copied to clipboard</string>
    <string name="incomplete">Incomplete</string>

    <string name="uz">O'zbek</string>
    <string name="en">English</string>
    <string name="ru">Russian</string>

    <string name="a1">Beginner (A1)</string>
    <string name="a2">Elementary (A2)</string>
    <string name="b1">Intermediate (B1)</string>
    <string name="b2">Upper Intermediate (B2)</string>
    <string name="c1">Advanced (C1)</string>
    <string name="c2">Proficiency (C2)</string>
    <string name="native">Native</string>

    <string name="welcome_text">Hey,  I am José</string>
    <string name="about_text">Motivated and adaptable eager to contribute and learn. Passionate Web Developer and UX/UI designer. Dedicated of Pixel Perfect web.</string>

    <string name="job_position_unical">Android Software Engineer</string>
    <string name="job_description_unical_0">Improved code quality and stability with increasing test coverage from 40% to 75% with unit and integration tests.</string>
    <string name="job_description_unical_1">Integrated CI/CD pipelines using GitHub Actions/GitLab CI to automate testing and deployment processes, reducing the release cycle time by 50% and enhancing deployment reliability</string>
    <string name="job_description_unical_2">Utilized code-driven approaches for UI creation to optimize performance and enable dynamic content handling</string>
    <string name="job_description_unical_3">Developed a Fragment-like component for screen management, incorporating swipe-to-close functionality and automatic landscape mode handling</string>
    <string name="job_description_unical_4">Implemented offline mode, allowing users to perform various tasks without internet connectivity. Utilized SQLite for local data storage and ensured seamless synchronization with the server upon reconnection.</string>
    <string name="job_description_unical_5">Implemented a robust logging system to track app behavior, monitor performance, and debug issues effectively, resulting in a 30% decrease in crash rates and a 25% increase in app stability.</string>
    <string name="job_description_unical_6">Implemented fare calculation in offline mode within a taxi driver application by utilizing location tracking and database caching functionalities.</string>
    <string name="job_description_unical_7">Developed an Android library optimized for interfacing with POS printers, capable of establishing connections via Bluetooth, USB, or Ethernet for seamless printing operations.</string>
    <string name="job_description_unical_8">Added a feature to an iOS application enabling printing of images in POS printers, expanding the app’s functionality and usability.</string>
    <string name="job_description_unical_9">Developed and collaborated on a Flutter-based desktop application, leading the creation of data and domain modules, database setup, and networking components within a cross-functional team environment.</string>

    <string name="job_position_upwork">Freelance Android Software Engineer</string>
    <string name="job_description_upwork_0">Collaborated directly with clients as a freelancer, understanding their requirements and delivering customized solutions to meet their needs.</string>
    <string name="job_description_upwork_1">Enhanced app UI to align with Material Design guidelines, incorporating intuitive animations for a more engaging user experience.</string>
    <string name="job_description_upwork_2">Transitioned legacy codebase to the MVVM architecture pattern, while adhering to clean architecture principles by modularizing code for improved maintainability and scalability.</string>
    <string name="job_description_upwork_3">Implemented advanced features such as read receipts, message info screen, and auto-delete functionality, similar to WhatsApp, within a chat application built on Firebase infrastructure, enhancing user engagement.</string>

    <string name="education_tuit_title">Tashkent University of Information Technologies</string>
    <string name="education_tuit_field">Software engineering</string>
    <string name="education_description_tuit_0">Algorithms and Data Structures, Operating Systems, development methodologies, Database management systems, development tools, and collaborative team projects</string>

    <string name="skill_1">Web Development</string>
    <string name="skill_1_item_1">HTML</string>
    <string name="skill_1_item_2">CSS</string>
    <string name="skill_1_item_3">JavaScript</string>
    <string name="skill_1_item_4">Tailwind</string>
    <string name="skill_2">Framework</string>
    <string name="skill_2_item_1">React</string>
    <string name="skill_2_item_2">Astro</string>

    <string name="project_description_bito">Bito is an all-in-one ERP app that streamlines and optimizes operations for businesses of any size or industry. It offers an integrated solution for managing key enterprise processes.</string>
    <string name="project_description_bito_0">Developed Bito, a ERP system from scratch, integrating modules for POS, inventory, finance, HR, logistics, and
supply chain management.</string>
    <string name="project_description_bito_1">Utilized Kotlin and Java in a multi-module MVVM architecture, employing Kotlin Coroutines for concurrency and
Room for database management.</string>
    <string name="project_description_bito_2">Implemented manual dependency injection, code-driven UI, and Firebase for real-time communication, following
Scrum methodology.</string>
    <string name="project_description_bito_3">Ensured high-quality code through CI/CD pipelines with GitLab Actions and thorough testing using JUnit and
Espresso.</string>

    <string name="project_description_taxi">Taxi Driver is a white-label mobile app that helps taxi drivers efficiently manage ride requests with features like real-time navigation, offline fare calculation, ride history, and driver ratings.</string>
    <string name="project_description_taxi_0">Developed Taxi Driver, a mobile app designed for taxi drivers to manage ride requests, offering real-time navigation, offline fare calculation, ride history, and a driver rating system.</string>
    <string name="project_description_taxi_1">Utilized Kotlin in an MVVM multi-module architecture, with Kotlin Coroutines for concurrency and Room for
database management.</string>
    <string name="project_description_taxi_2">Implemented Hilt for dependency injection, WebSocket and Firebase for real-time communication, and
OpenStreetMap (OSM) for navigation services.</string>
    <string name="project_description_taxi_3">Ensured seamless development using GitLab Actions for CI/CD, with a user interface built in XML.</string>

    <string name="project_description_market">Market is a white-label e-commerce app offering a wide range of products—from groceries to electronics—with intuitive navigation, secure payments, and smooth order management for a seamless shopping experience.</string>
    <string name="project_description_market_0">Developed the Market app, an e-commerce platform allowing users to browse, search, and purchase
products across categories such as groceries, electronics, fashion, and home goods.</string>
    <string name="project_description_market_1">Utilized Kotlin in a multi-module MVVM architecture with Kotlin Coroutines for concurrency, Room for database
management, and Hilt for dependency injection.</string>
    <string name="project_description_market_2">Integrated WebSocket and Firebase for real-time communication and followed Scrum methodology for agile
development.</string>

    <string name="project_description_autostatus">A Telegram web app that allows Premium users to customize their status with auto-changing emojis based on predefined time intervals.</string>

</resources>